https://www.forrelationshiphelp.com/privacy-policy/

The “How’s My Relationship” Checklist
Is My Partner a Toxic Hijackal?
Support Circle
Join Today!
Verbal Abuse And How To Stop It
What are Personality Disorders?
The “How’s My Relationship” Checklist
Is My Partner a Toxic Hijackal?
Support Circle
Join Today!
Verbal Abuse And How To Stop It
What are Personality Disorders?
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, follow or comment on a blog post, or respond to a survey.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To improve our website: we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you
To improve customer service: your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs
To process transactions: Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list or follow the blog posts, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. To STOP following blog posts, you must de-register from the website itself. You can do that by using the "profile" link under the "follow" heading in the sidebar.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.
All product & service orders are processed via Paypal, which provides & maintains its own secure server & SSL (secure socket layer), or Authorize.net over our SSL. No personal payment information is ever transmitted via Optimize Life Now LLC from ForRelationshipHelp.com or any other domain owned by Rhoberta Shaler, PhD and Optimize Life Now, LLC.
Do we use cookies?
About Cookies
We use cookies on forrelationshiphelp.com for a number of purposes. They help us to provide you with a good experience when you browse this website. They also allow us to improve our site and deliver to you a website you want to browse and enjoy.
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
By continuing to browse the site, you agree to the use of cookies as detailed below.
First, what is a cookie?
A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that I/we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer. You can find more information about web cookies here: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie
We use the following cookies:
Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are required for you to use the features available on this website. They include, for example, the ability to login and post a comment.
Analytical/performance cookies.  These cookies allow us to recognize, track, and count the number of visitors who come to this website. They also allow us to track broken pages on the website and to count what visitors do when they click through the website.
Functionality cookies. These cookies allow us to track and remember your preferences for our website. For example, when you're logged in, we can greet you by name and/or remember your preferences (such as your choice of language or region).
We use two different kinds of cookies on this website: First party and third party cookies (both defined in detail on the wikipedia link above).
First-party cookies
These cookies are specifically about forrelationshiphelp.com and track your usage of this website. These cookies are considered essential for the website to operate correctly. These cookies, none of which capture personally identifiable information, include:
Visitor ID – this cookie is a numeric value that identifies unique visitors and provides coherence and consistency to a site visit- it is anonymous and contains no personally identifying information;
Page number – this cookie identifies the page you are on;
Session ID – this cookie identifies your website session;
Test – this cookie checks whether or not your browser supports cookies;
Third-party cookies
This website sets different types of third-party cookies to track usage, social sharing and more. These cookies are not under my/our control, and serve to help us understand the visitors who come to the website, as well as support our connection to other third party sites.  (Again, see the wikipedia page above for detailed explanations of third party services/cookies).
Included in our list of third-party cookies are the following services:
Google Analytics –Google Analytics is used to collect data about website usage. This data does not include personally identifiable information. Data is stored anonymously for 14 months and per Google’s policies, this data is automatically deleted after 14 months. You can view Google’s Privacy Policy here: www.google.com/policies/privacy/.
Social sharing plugin– a cookie is used when you use the social sharing service on our website to share a link with LinkedIn, Facebook, Twitter, etc.  More information about the Sharing app privacy policy can be found here: https://jetpack.com/support/privacy/.
Mailchimp - our newsletter management service. https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/
My webinars and private sessions are provided via Zoom Video Conferenceing. Free webinars are provided in exchange for being placed on one of the aforementioned Mailchimp mailing lists. The privacy policy for Zoom can be viewed at : https://zoom.us/privacy
Any payments for any products or informational items are processed securely via PayPal. PayPal’s privacy policy is listed at : https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full
Booking private sessions, webinars & group coaching is processed through AcuityScheduling.com. AcuityScheduling.com's privacy policy is listed at: https://acuityscheduling.com/privacy.php
Payments for private sessions, webinars & group coaching are processed through Authorize.net. Authorize.net's privacy policy is listed at: https://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/
Many of our books & ebooks are sold through Amazon. Amazon's privacy policy is here: https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=footer_privacy?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496
Your rights with cookies:
Cookies are set by many entities and may include the website’s owners/developers/managers, plugins, third-party providers, advertisers and anyone else who collects or uses the website’s data.
As a user of this (or any) website, you can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of some, or all cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of the site.
To learn how to block cookies, simply go to Google and type in “how do I block cookies” on whatever browser you use (Chrome, Firefox etc.) and you will find the details needed to block some or all cookies on your browser.
Additional data storage and privacy policy considerations
In addition to the non-personally identifiable data collected by cookies, this website also offers the ability to contact with us via contact forms, newsletter registration forms, downloadable ebooks, free downloadable gifts, webinars and other similar files.
To receive free gifts from this website, we require that you share your personal information consisting of your first and last name and your email address, and in some cases, your city. In some cases we have additional optional fields to tell us about (how often you'd like to receive newsletters, other information you'd like to receive, etc). In most cases, information is gathered and stored in the website database or via a third-party service (Mailchimp, Google Analytics, Paypal).  All information gathered via any form on this website can be deleted upon request.
Information and informational items are provided in exchange for adding your email address and possibly your name, business and or website information to one of our mailing lists. All mailing lists are stored and executed via Mailchimp for the sole purpose of communicating information, as well as occasional marketing of services and products. Each mailing list will specifically detail what type of emails you may receive and possibly the frequency. You may unsubscribe from said email list(s) at any time by using the unsubscribe link provided in every email.
Your information is never shared or sold to others for marketing purposes, and is only shared with third party services as necessary and explained above. If at any time you wish to opt out of communication, email, or to have your data deleted, please direct your request to the email, address and/or phone number below.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses, for example, your keyword searches on our site will be accessed by Google to serve more appropriate ads when you are visiting us. These are in no way tied to your personal information, nor are they retained after you leave our site.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
GDPR Compliance
To the best of our known ability we are in compliance with GDPR.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our websites.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
This policy was last modified on May 17, 2018.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
email: assist@forrelationshiphelp.com
Optimize Life Now, LLC
979 Woodland Parkway, Suite 101-128,
Lost your password?
Search Knowledgebase
Ask A Question?
Log In is required for submitting new question.
Login
Username or Email Address
Password
Remember Me
Lost Your Password?
Register
Don't have an account? Register one!
Yes, I want to receive updates via email.
Registration confirmation will be emailed to you.
